#### Jonathon Van Ausdal

jonathonvanausdal257@gmail.com 385.484.1260

## Summary

Software Engineer with experience in a MERN environment. Highly motivated. I work well on a team or solo. demonstrated working knowledge of Bootstrap, CSS, Express.js, Git, Github, Heroku, HTML (HTML5), JavaScript, JQuery, MongoDB, MySQL, Node.js, React, SEO, Responsive Design, API/JSON, RESTful API, State Management, Command Line, Database Theory, Agile Methodologies, Quality Assurance Testing, Social Coding Best Practices, Computer Science Fundamentals

Portfolio Link: https://jonathonvanausdal9915.github.io/Myportfolio/#

Website Link: https://paneless-windows.herokuapp.com/#/home

# Core Technologies

React

- CSS
- JavaScript
- Agile Scrum
- HTML

- Node.js
- Express.js
- Apollo/Graphql
- MongoDb/MySQL

### Experience

#### **University of Utah Coding Bootcamp Program**

January 2022 – Present

Salt Lake City, Utah

- Created a portfolio for class assignments and projects.
- Worked solo and on a team.
- Experience with using Github, Heroku and Github Pages.
- Introduced to MySQL and MongoDB.
- Ensure teams follow design patterns and frameworks using shared APIs

#### Pane-less Window Washing

May 2022 – September 2022

American Fork, Utah

- Create and Maintain a website for Pane-less Window washing.
- Implemented using MERN stack. (MongoDB, Express, React, Node).

#### **Down Town Furniture**

**August** 2020 – January 2021

Saint George, Utah

- Operated a propane forklift and Baltimore lift.
- Responsible for delivering furniture in a quickly and timely manner.
- Operated box truck safely.
- Responsible for stocking the store floor with furniture to be sold.
- Used hand tools to assemble furniture.

**University of Utah** 



**Web Site Development** 

**Furniture Delivery** 

Always used safety precautions to lift and transport heavy furniture.

# Education

- American Fork High School 2017
- One year of study at UVU towards Computer Science.
- University of Utah Web Coding Bootcamp Program November 2022
- Self-directed learner

### References

- Taylor Down Town Furniture (435) 628-5812)
- Jonah Down Town Furniture(385)292-2487)
- Max Clearlink(801)855-5136)